Guide to the New York University Archives Audiovisual Collection AV
New York University Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - Law School Bicentennial [8 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV146 (Box 3, Reel AV146, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV146)
  - Law School Bicentennial [10 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV148 (Box 3, Reel AV148, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV148)
  - Law School Bicentennial [1 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV149 (Box 3, Reel AV149, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV149)
  - Law School Bicentennial [2 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV150 (Box 3, Reel AV150, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV150)
  - Law School Bicentennial [3 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV151 (Box 3, Reel AV151, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV151)
  - Law School Bicentennial [4 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV152 (Box 3, Reel AV152, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV152)
  - Law School Bicentennial [5 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV153 (Box 4, Reel AV153, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV153)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 33 min.
  - Law School Bicentennial [6 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV154 (Box 4, Reel AV154, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV154)
  - Law School Bicentennial [7 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV155 (Box 4, Reel AV155, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV155)
  - Law School Bicentennial [8 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV156 (Box 4, Reel AV156, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV156)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 34 min.
  - Law School Bicentennial [9 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV157 (Box 4, Reel AV157, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV157)
  - Law School Bicentennial [10 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV158 (Box 4, Reel AV158, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV158)
  - Law School Bicentennial [11 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV159 (Box 4, Reel AV159, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV159)
  - Law School Bicentennial [12 of 12], 1976-04-30; AV160 (Box 4, Reel AV160, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV160)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 25 min.
  - Speech at School of Law, 1960; AV161; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994 (Box 4, Reel AV161, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV161)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 83 min.
    New York University. School of Law
  - Broadcasting and the Law Seminar - Jerome Boris, Undated; AV162 (Box 4, Reel AV162, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV162)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 76 min.
  - Alcohol Conference, 1974-06-24; AV163 (Box 4, Reel AV163, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV163)
  - Art Critics [1], 1974-12-10; AV164 (Box 4, Reel AV164, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV164)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 97 min.
  - Art Critics [2], 1974-12-10; AV165 (Box 4, Reel AV165, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV165)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 7 min.
  - Art Critics [2], 1975-02-18; AV166 (Box 4, Reel AV166, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV166)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 8 min.
  - Art Critics [2], 1975-03-11; AV167 (Box 4, Reel AV167, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV167)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 12 min.
  - Art Critics [1], 1975-11-19; AV168 (Box 4, Reel AV168, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV168)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 96 min.
  - Art Critics [2], 1975-11-19; AV169 (Box 4, Reel AV169, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV169)
  - Art Critics [1], 1975-01-21; AV170 (Box 4, Reel AV170, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV170)
  - Art Critics in Residence - Carter Radcliff [1], 1974-10-29; AV171 (Box 4, Reel AV171, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV171)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 98 min.
  - Art Critics in Residence - Carter Radcliff [2], 1974-10-29; AV172 (Box 4, Reel AV172, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV172)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 20 min.
  - Art Critics in Residence [2], 1975-05-06; AV173 (Box 4, Reel AV173, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV173)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 13 min.
  - BPA Convocation Paes. Hester, 1974-09-16; AV174 (Box 4, Reel AV174, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV174)
  - "Weisman" taped for Dental Dinner, Undated; AV175 (Box 4, Reel AV175, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV175)
  - Graduation [1], 1975-06-05; AV176 (Box 4, Reel AV176, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV176)
  - Graduation [2], 1975-06-05; AV177 (Box 4, Reel AV177, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV177)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 63 min.
  - Graduation [4], 1975-06-05; AV178 (Box 4, Reel AV178, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV178)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 33 min., Preservation note: Duplicate of AV176 and AV177.
  - ITT Tape Master [1], 1974-03-14; AV179 (Box 4, Reel AV179, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV179)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 66 min.
  - ITT Lecture Master [2], 1974-03-14; AV180 (Box 4, Reel AV180, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV180)
  - ITT [1], 1974-04-04; AV181 (Box 4, Reel AV181, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV181)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 60 min., Preservation note: "
  - ITT [2], 1974-04-04; AV182 (Box 4, Reel AV182, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV182)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 32 min.
  - Maison Francais, 1975-02-14; AV183 (Box 4, Reel AV183, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV183)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 91 min.
  - N.Y.U. Campaign Reel 1, Undated; AV184 (Box 4, Reel AV184, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV184)
  - N.Y.U. Campaign Reel 2, Undated; AV185 (Box 4, Reel AV185, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV185)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 26 min.
  - NYU - Share [1], 1975-03-05; AV186 (Box 4, Reel AV186, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV186)
  - NYU - Share [2], 1975-03-05; AV187 (Box 4, Reel AV187, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV187)
  - NYU - Share [3], 1975-03-05; AV188 (Box 4, Reel AV188, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV188)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 30 min.
  - Dr. T. Melady, Mr. R. Wood, + Mr. F. Weaver, interviewed by Fr. Anthony Mills of Vatican Radio on RACISM (Rome World Congress for Lay Apostolate) - Part 1, Undated; AV189 (Box 4, Reel AV189, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV189)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 22 min.
  - Sawhill Press Conference, 1975-04-21; AV192 (Box 4, Reel AV192, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV192)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 17 min.
  - President Sawhill's Investiture, 1975-11-20; AV193 (Box 4, Reel AV193, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV193)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 71 min.
  - Institutional Facilities, President Sawhill WSCUC Faculty Meeting, 1976-05-03; AV194 (Box 5, Reel AV194, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV194)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 43 min.
  - Women's Career Conference, Part I, 1976-04-24; AV195 (Box 5, Reel AV195, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV195)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 65 mins.
  - Women's Career Conference, Part II, 1976-04-24; AV196 (Box 5, Reel AV196, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV196)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 24 mins.
  - Institutional Facilities, Dr. Isabel Sawhill, Women in Management Series, Part I, 1976-02-07; AV197 (Box 5, Reel AV197, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV197)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 52 mins.
  - Institutional Facilities, Dr. Isabel Sawhill, Women in Management Series, Part II, 1976-02-07; AV198 (Box 5, Reel AV198, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV198)
  - Women in Media, Part I, 1974-12-07; AV199 (Box 5, Reel AV199, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV199)
  - Women in Media, Part II, 1974-12-07; AV200 (Box 5, Reel AV200, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV200)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 66 mins.
  - Women in Media, Part III, 1974-12-07; AV201 (Box 5, Reel AV201, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV201)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 64 mins.
  - Women in Media, Part VI, 1974-12-07; AV202 (Box 5, Reel AV202, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV202)
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker, Part I, 1976-04-20; AV203 (Box 5, Reel AV203, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV203)
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker, Part II, 1976-04-20; AV204 (Box 5, Reel AV204, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV204)
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker, Part I, 1976-04-21; AV205 (Box 5, Reel AV205, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV205)
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker, Part II, 1976-04-21; AV206 (Box 5, Reel AV206, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV206)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 44 mins.
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker Luncheon, Part I, 1976-04-21; AV207 (Box 5, Reel AV207, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV207)
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker Luncheon, Part II, 1976-04-21; AV208 (Box 5, Reel AV208, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV208)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 39 mins.
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker, Part I, 1976-04-22; AV209 (Box 5, Reel AV209, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV209)
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker, Part II, 1976-04-22; AV210 (Box 5, Reel AV210, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV210)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 56 mins.
  - Institutional Facilities, Peter Drucker Luncheon, Part III, 1976-04-22; AV211 (Box 5, Reel AV211, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV211)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 32 mins.
  - [With Mayor Lindsay], 1970-11-08; AV212 (Box 5, Reel AV212, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV212)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 34 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1976: The "Business and the American Economy, 1776-2001 ITT Lectures, 'Evolving Role of Banking and Monetary Policy' with Andrew F. Brimmer, Harvard GBA, Part 1, 1976-02-25; AV213 (Box 5, Reel AV213, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV213)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 31 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1976: The "Business and the American Economy, 1776-2001 ITT Lectures, 'Evolving Role of Banking and Monetary Policy' with Andrew F. Brimmer, Harvard GBA, Part 2, 1976-02-25; AV214 (Box 5, Reel AV214, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV214)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 30 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1976: The "Business and the American Economy, 1776-20001 ITT Lectures, 'Relationships Between Government and Business' with Carl Kaysen, Director of the Institute for Advanced Study, Princeton University, Part 1, 1975-10-22; AV215 (Box 5, Reel AV215, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV215)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 28 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1976: The "Business and the American Economy, 1776-20001 ITT Lectures, 'Relationships Between Government and Business' with Carl Kaysen, Director of the Institute for Advanced Study, Princeton University, Part 2, 1975-10-22; AV216 (Box 5, Reel AV216, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV216)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 33 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1976: "The Economic System in an Age of Discontinuity: Long-Range Planning or Market Reliance?" with Profs. Wassily Leontieff, NYU and Herbert Stein, Univ. of Virginia, Part I, 1976-04-26; AV217 (Box 5, Reel AV217, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV217)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 27 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1976: The "Business and the American Economy, 1776-20001 ITT Lectures, 'Relationships Between Government and Business' with Carl Kaysen, Director of the Institute for Advanced Study, Princeton University, Part 2, 1976-04-26; AV218 (Box 5, Reel AV218, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV218)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 29 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1976: PGM #11 "We Hold These Truths: The American Credo - The English Foundations" with Prof. Thomas Payne Govan, Prof. of History, Oregon U., Part I, 1976-04-12; AV222 (Box 5, Reel AV222, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV222)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1977: PGM #12 "We Hold These Truths: The American Credo - The English Foundations" with Prof. Thomas Payne Govan, Prof. of History, Oregon U., Part II, 1976-04-12; AV223 (Box 5, Reel AV223, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV223)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1977: "Irony in Literature" Part I, 1977-05-16; AV219 (Box 5, Reel AV219, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV219)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1977: "Irony in Literature" Part II, 1977-05-16; AV220 (Box 5, Reel AV220, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV220)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 1977:"Irony in Literature" Part III, 1977-05-16; AV221 (Box 5, Reel AV221, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV221)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration 23 mins.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "The American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" Series presents, 'World Order or World Conflict: Can the Earth be Shared?' with Sen. James Abourezk (S.D.), Rep. Lester R. Wolff (NY), and David Halberstam, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter and author., Part I, 1975-10-06; AV224 (Box 5, Reel AV224, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV224)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'The Strategy of Alliances: Reflections and Projections.' Part I, 1975-12-15; AV225 (Box 5, Reel AV225, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV225)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'The Strategy of Alliances: Reflections and Projections.' Part II, 1975-12-15; AV226 (Box 5, Reel AV226, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV226)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'NATO and American Interests: A Reassessment" Part I, 1975-12-22; AV227 (Box 5, Reel AV227, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV227)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'NATO and American Interests: A Reassessment" Part II, 1975-12-22; AV228 (Box 5, Reel AV228, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV228)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'Power, Secrecy and Accountability: Dilemma of an 'Open Society.', 1975-12-29; AV229 (Box 5, Reel AV229, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV229)
  - The NYU Lecture Series: "The American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era Series" presents, 'Congressional vs. Presidential Power--The Tenuous Balance.' Reel I of II., 1975-1976; AV231 (Box 6, Reel AV231)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 27 min. 40 sec.
    Housing annotations: The lecture series program is included with the tape.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'Power, Secrecy and Accountability: Dilemma of an 'Open Society.' Reel II of II., 1975-1976; AV230 (Box 6, Reel AV230)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 29 min. 52 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series: "The American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era Series" presents, 'Congressional vs. Presidential Power--The Tenuous Balance.' Reel II of II., 1975-1976; AV232 (Box 6, Reel AV232)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 30 min. 08 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "Newspapers: The World at Your Doorstep" panel discussion from the Media 78 Conference. Reel I of II., 1978-09-28; AV233 (Box 6, Reel AV233)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 29 min. 00 sec.
    Housing annotations: "WNYU-AM, Rebroadcast, 3/24/81, 7-8pm." The lecture series program is included with the tape.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "Newspapers: The World at Your Doorstep" panel discussion from the Media 78 Conference. Reel II of II., 1978-09-28; AV234 (Box 6, Reel AV234)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 23 min. 36 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "World Order or World Conflict: Can the Earth be Shared?" Reel II of II., 1975-1976; AV235 (Box 6, Reel AV235)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 27 min. 30 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 76 PGM #3: "Business and the American Economy, 1776-2001" ITT series presents, 'Role of Business in U.S. Economic Growth.' with Roger M. Blough, partner, White and Case. Reel I of II., 1975-11-18; AV236 (Box 6, Reel AV236)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 28 min. 48 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 76 PGM #3: "Business and the American Economy, 1776-2001" ITT series presents, 'Role of Business in U.S. Economic Growth.' with Roger M. Blough, partner, White and Case. Reel II of II., 1975-11-18; AV237 (Box 6, Reel AV237)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 29 min. 32 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 76: "The Evolving Role of Accounting." ITT Lecture #5, Michael Schiff, Vincent C. Ross Professor of Accounting, NYU. Reel I of II., 1976-02-04; AV238 (Box 6, Reel AV238)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 29 min. 40 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 76: "The Evolving Role of Accounting." ITT Lecture #5, Michael Schiff, Vincent C. Ross Professor of Accounting, NYU. Reel II of II., 1976-02-04; AV239 (Box 6, Reel AV239)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 29 min. 44 sec.
  - Commencement 1981 - Part 1 of 4, 1981-06-04; AV240 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel AV240)
    Duration: 32 minutes
  - Commencement 1981 - Part 2 of 4, 1981-06-04; AV241 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel AV241)
  - Commencement 1981 - Part 3 of 4, 1981-06-04; AV242 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel AV242)
    Duration: 31 minutes
  - Commencement 1981 - Part 4 of 4, 1981-06-04; AV243 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel AV243)
    Duration: 16 minutes
  - "NYU 147th Commencement From Washington Square Park." Reel I of III., 1979-06-07; AV244 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel AV244)
  - "NYU 147th Commencement From Washington Square Park." Reel II of III., 1979-06-07; AV245 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel AV245)
  - "NYU 147th Commencement From Washington Square Park." Reel III of III., 1979-06-07; AV246 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel AV246)
    Duration: 29 minutes
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #4: "Baroque Musical Ideas." Reel I of I., 1975-06-25; AV247 (Box 6, Reel AV247)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 28 min. 30 sec.
    Housing annotations: "WNYU-FM BDCST 6-25-75, 8:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #5: "Concertos and Sonatas." Reel I of I., 1975-07-02; AV248 (Box 6, Reel AV248)
    Housing annotations: "WNYU-FM BDCST 7-2-75, 8:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #6: "The Classical Symphony." Reel I of I., 1975-07-09; AV249 (Box 6, Reel AV249)
    Housing annotations: "WNYU BDCST 7-9-75, 8:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #7: "What is an Opera?" Reel I of I., 1975-07-16; AV250 (Box 6, Reel AV250)
    Housing annotations: "WNYU-FM BDCST 7-16-75, 8:30pm" marked on containerl label in red ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #8: "Music in the Last Century." Reel I of I., 1975-07-23; AV251 (Box 6, Reel AV251)
    Housing annotations: "WNYU BDCST 7-23-75, 8:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #13: "Music in Our Time." Reel I of I., 1975-08-27; AV252 (Box 6, Reel AV252)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 28 min. 20 sec.
    Housing annotation: "WNYU BDCST 8-27-75, 8:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #1: "What is an Orchestra?" Reel I of I., 1975-06-04; AV253 (Box 6, Reel AV253)
    Housing annotation: "WNYU BDCST 6-4-75, 8:30pm" marked on container box in ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #2: "Old, Old Music." Reel I of I., 1975-06-11; AV254 (Box 6, Reel AV254)
    Housing annotation: "WNYU BDCST 6-11-75, 8:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - Listen, I Dare You! Program #3: "The Wonderful Renaissance." Reel I of I., 1975-06-18; AV255 (Box 6, Reel AV255)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio
    Housing annotation: "WNYU BDCST 6-18-75, 8:30pm" marked on container in red ink.
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #1., 1975-03-15; AV256 (Box 6, Reel AV256)
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #2., 1975-03-15; AV257 (Box 6, Reel AV257)
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #3., 1975-03-15; AV258 (Box 6, Reel AV258)
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #4., 1975-03-15; AV259 (Box 6, Reel AV259)
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #5., 1975-03-15; AV260 (Box 6, Reel AV260)
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #6, 1975-03-15; AV261 (Box 6, Reel AV261)
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #7, 1975-03-15; AV262 (Box 6, Reel AV262)
  - Non Fiction Writers Workshop, Loeb Student Center, NYU, Tape #8, 1975-03-15; AV263 (Box 6, Reel AV263)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'Superpower-Detente and the Emerging Worlds.' Reel I of II., 1975-11-03; AV264 (Box 7, Reel AV264)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall 1975: "American Foreign Policy in the Post-Vietnam Era" presents, 'Superpower-Detente and the Emerging Worlds.' Reel II of II., 1975-11-03; AV265 (Box 9, Reel AV265)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 28 min. 00 sec.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall Semester 1982 PGM #4: "The Principle of Hope." Professor Joyce Appleby, author and historian. Reel II of II., 1982-10-13; 1983-01-04; AV266 (Box 8, Reel AV266)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 27 min. 00 sec.
    Housing annotations: The lecture series program is included with the tape. For Air 1/4/83, 8:30-9:30 PM
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall Semester 1982 PGM #4: "The Principle of Hope." Professor Joyce Appleby, author and historian. Reel I of II., 1982-10-13; 1983-01-04; AV267 (Box 8, Reel AV267)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 29 min. 10 sec.
    Housing annotation: For Air 1/4/83, 8:30-9:30 PM
  - "The Value of a Liberal Arts Education." A documentary produced by the NYU Communications Arts Documentary Workshop., 1978-06-01; AV268 (Box 8, Reel AV268)
    Format: 1/4" open reel audio, Duration: 29 min. 30 sec.
    Housing annotation: "WNYU BDCST 6-1-78, 9:30-10pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - University Broadcast Lab: And Now a Word from Our Sponsor, 1978 May 22; AV269; 1 reel (Box 8, Reel 269, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 50)
  - Commencement 1983 - Part 1 of 4, AV270 (Box 7, Reel AV270, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV270)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 14 min.
  - Commencement 1983 - Part 2 of 4, AV271 (Box 7, Reel AV271, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV271)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 29 min.
  - Commencement 1983 - Part 3 of 4, AV272 (Box 7, Reel AV272, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV272)
  - Commencement 1983 - Part 4 of 4, AV273 (Box 7, Reel AV273, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV273)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 18 min.
  - Art Critics in Residence - Kosloff. Reel I of II., 1972-07-05; AV277 (Box 7, Reel AV277, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV277)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 28 min.
  - Art Critics in Residence - Kosloff. Reel II of II., 1972-07-05; AV278 (Box 7, Reel AV278, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV278)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "A Memo to Media: Our Hate/Care Relationship" with Tom Brokaw and Frank Shakespeare. Reel I of II., 1978-09-28; AV279 (Box 7, Reel AV279, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV279)
    Housing annotation: "Rerun 3/3/81 7-8 pm." From the Media 78 Conference.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "A Memo to Media: Our Hate/Care Relationship" with Tom Brokaw and Frank Shakespeare. Reel II of II., 1978-09-28; AV280 (Box 7, Reel AV280, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV280)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 24 min.